

Mirpur-12,

Dhaka-1206

Phone:

WhatsApp

Dhaka cantonment,

+880-1571350890

+880-1571350890

Ambition

Asraful Islam

To Work dynamically in a challenging environment where innovative ideas are encouraged & also to develop a high-profile career with an organization where the inherent aptitude and persuasiveness will be optimally utilized. Company best ambition job-related. I'm a self-starter with a can-do attitude that makes me a confident LEADER in this Industry.

Career Summary

I worked for many reputed companies and earned enough knowledge in the field of your given post. I think I am the most eligible candidate for your given post.

Experience - 1 Year 6 month

Buddies arena resturent

01 November 2024 to currently working Cashier

Private study zone coaching (psz)

5 October 2023 to 11 September 2023 Teacher (Department subject)

Jhatika trades limited

01 august 2023 to 25 september 2023
Office assistant



mdasrafulislamfahim2 003@gmail.com



https://www.facebook.c om/fahimboss007/

Operating System:

- Windows XP, windows 10, windows 8, windows 7.
- Office Management.
- All Type PC Software install.

Key Strengths

- Communication Skills
- Time Management.

Educational Qualifications

Bhola Polytechnic Institute [Bhola, Barishal, Bangladesh] Diploma in Engineering

Computer Technology CGPA:3.74 out of 4.00 Session:2019-2020

Muladi M.G high school [Muladi, Barisal, Bangladesh] Secondary School Certificate (SSC)(Vocational)

Building Maintanance GPA: 4.36 out of 5.00 Pass Year: 2019

- Leadership
- > Teamwork
- Active listening
- Problem solving
- Critical Thinking

References

Name: Md Rakib Hossen Instructor (Automobile) Technical training centre Panchagarh Hello:01876601500 Email:

mirakib2013@gmail.com

Asraful Islam

Professional Training

Cisco Certified Network Associate (CCNA) + Office Management. Genuity training center. o1 September 2023 to 12 December

Volunteer Actives

Bangladesh Scout Member.

2023.

Good Neighbors NGO Volunteer

Personal Details

Father's Name: Md Eshak Peda Mother's Name: Mst. Aklima Begum

Date of Birth: 20-12-2003 Marital Status: Single Nationality: Bangladesh Passport Number: N/A Driving License: N/A NID No: 5122408619

Birth registration no: 20030616279110735

Religion: Islam

Present Address: House: - Moitri tower, Dhaka cantonment-1206, Dhaka Permanent Address: Asholi Sontoshpur, Kazirhat, Mehedigong-8270, Barisal.

Languages

Bengali: Fluency

English: Fluency in speaking and well as reading & Writing.

Personal Interests

Photography, Travelling, Working, Mobile Games, Reading, Writing, Sports, Volunteering, Coding, Foreign language etc.

I do, Hereby declare that the above statements are correct and complete to best of my knowledge.

